#### Contact

bushrazohaib84@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/bushra-zohaib-0a2860269 (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

Data Entry
Sales and Marketing
Product Marketing

#### Certifications

Responsive Web Design

# Bushra Zohaib

Transforming Healthcare & Pharma with Al Innovation | Specializing in Digital Health, Precision Medicine, and Customized Web Solutions - Let's Shape the Future Together!

Karāchi, Sindh, Pakistan

# Summary

Welcome to my LinkedIn profile.

With experience in pharmaceuticals and a focus on AI, I am committed to pushing the boundaries of healthcare innovation. I specialize in integrating AI technologies to optimize pharmaceutical research and healthcare solutions. Let's connect to explore opportunities to drive transformative advancements in AI and healthcare together.

# Experience

Governor Sindh Initiative for GenAI, Web3, and Metaverse Junior Teacher February 2024 - Present (9 months)

Sindh, Pakistan

#### **PIAIC**

Student

November 2023 - Present (1 year)

Pakistan

Gourcey Pharma

**Product Manager** 

October 2008 - December 2008 (3 months)

Pakistan

### **NEUCON PHARMA PVT.LTD**

Marketing Coordinator

January 2005 - September 2008 (3 years 9 months)

Karachi Division, Sindh, Pakistan

Geofman Pharmaceuticals

**Production Pharmacist** 

June 2004 - December 2004 (7 months)

Page 1 of 2

Karachi Division, Sindh, Pakistan

Geeco pharma
Data Entry Specialist
June 2001 - June 2004 (3 years 1 month)
Pakistan

Worked as Pharmacist data control in Geeco medilab directory

## Education

### **PIAIC**

Al and Cloud Engineer, Artificial Intelligence · (November 2023 - November 2024)

Jinnah University for Women

B.Pharm, Pharmacy · (March 2000 - March 2004)

Govt.girls High School Rohri